[
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 1 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "1 x 1", "answer": "1", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 2", "answer": "2", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 3", "answer": "3", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 4", "answer": "4", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 5", "answer": "5", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 6", "answer": "6", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 7", "answer": "7", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 8", "answer": "8", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 9", "answer": "9", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "1 x 10", "answer": "10", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 2 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "2 x 1", "answer": "2", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 2", "answer": "4", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 3", "answer": "6", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 4", "answer": "8", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 5", "answer": "10", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 6", "answer": "12", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 7", "answer": "14", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 8", "answer": "16", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 9", "answer": "18", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "2 x 10", "answer": "20", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 3 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "3 x 1", "answer": "3", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 2", "answer": "6", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 3", "answer": "9", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 4", "answer": "12", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 5", "answer": "15", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 6", "answer": "18", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 7", "answer": "21", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 8", "answer": "24", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 9", "answer": "27", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "3 x 10", "answer": "30", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 4 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "4 x 1", "answer": "4", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 2", "answer": "8", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 3", "answer": "12", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 4", "answer": "16", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 5", "answer": "20", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 6", "answer": "24", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 7", "answer": "28", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 8", "answer": "32", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 9", "answer": "36", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "4 x 10", "answer": "40", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 5 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "5 x 1", "answer": "5", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 2", "answer": "10", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 3", "answer": "15", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 4", "answer": "20", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 5", "answer": "25", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 6", "answer": "30", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 7", "answer": "35", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 8", "answer": "40", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 9", "answer": "45", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "5 x 10", "answer": "50", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 6 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "6 x 1", "answer": "6", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 2", "answer": "12", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 3", "answer": "18", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 4", "answer": "24", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 5", "answer": "30", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 6", "answer": "36", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 7", "answer": "42", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 8", "answer": "48", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 9", "answer": "54", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "6 x 10", "answer": "60", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 7 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "7 x 1", "answer": "7", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 2", "answer": "14", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 3", "answer": "21", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 4", "answer": "28", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 5", "answer": "35", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 6", "answer": "42", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 7", "answer": "49", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 8", "answer": "56", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 9", "answer": "63", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "7 x 10", "answer": "70", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 8 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "8 x 1", "answer": "8", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 2", "answer": "16", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 3", "answer": "24", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 4", "answer": "32", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 5", "answer": "40", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 6", "answer": "48", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 7", "answer": "56", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 8", "answer": "64", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 9", "answer": "72", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "8 x 10", "answer": "80", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 9 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "9 x 1", "answer": "9", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 2", "answer": "18", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 3", "answer": "27", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 4", "answer": "36", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 5", "answer": "45", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 6", "answer": "54", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 7", "answer": "63", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 8", "answer": "72", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 9", "answer": "81", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "9 x 10", "answer": "90", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Matte - 10 Multiplikation",
    "flashcards": [
      { "question": "10 x 1", "answer": "10", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 2", "answer": "20", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 3", "answer": "30", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 4", "answer": "40", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 5", "answer": "50", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 6", "answer": "60", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 7", "answer": "70", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 8", "answer": "80", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 9", "answer": "90", "isCorrect": false },
      { "question": "10 x 10", "answer": "100", "isCorrect": false }
    ]
  }
]
